What does a really severe looking backward another video?
So up until now, we return verdicts like this or the Department for Mobile, and the first one is either
the full delivering app.
So for this project, I have to ask for you or you can say or test so that what you have to do is that
so I have this wire frame.
So this is a wire frame for a music player, so they could have first it and make your own music player
using this white frame.
You can name it whatever you want.
You can place your preferred songs over here and take inspiration from like Spotify all the way to music.
And you can use any color you want, or if you want to, like, make a clone of Spotify.
You can also do that, so it all depends on you.
If something were not able to do this, I'm going to also create that for the after this video.
So stay tuned for that.
So if you're concerned, then go for it and make this project.
So this is what we do, and I was always in the next one.