To improve studio, I give this wireframe to you.
I know some offshore might done that project.
So who made that project?
Who can share that project on your story in the Instagram and you can take me with you.
You can see my Instagram I.D. also.
And you can also share that project on our Discord server.
Then our storm can take inspiration from your project.
Those who not build that project.
So let's make a project for them.
So let's create a new one.
So I'm going to make music for it.
It is kind of it sounds like.
I know it to sound like Spotify because I took inspiration from Spotify, so I literally we can take
inspiration from Spotify, audio, music or any you will or any your favorite music player so as to
the frame.
Currently, we are how iPhone 13 Max, so we are going to choose this one.
Let's look at our wild thing.
So we have things like profile picture logo on the hamburger menu and so on and so on.
So let's clear those things.
OK, now let's create a logo for our music player.
So now what do we have to do this time to create this section for our image and also for our song?
So this is a.
So anything we have to be is there to add these icons like a dislike, it's like open labor and pause
button and foul and make button.
So let's get those weapons.
Now it is the dark mode is really famous and lots of people are using them.
I'm also one of them, so let's clear their dark mode.
But before we make the dark mode, so let's do the color of these buttons, like if I applied the dark
mode on the frame so everything is going to be black.
So our buttons like play pause button, hot button and the dislike button is not going to be visible.
So let's make some changes or you?
If you want to, you can just sit this like three things like a play pause button and forward and backward
button, and you can change the color of the heart button and it's just like button.
You can like, make them white and and these three things would be blue.
So it really depends on you.
Soon, the color of the hamburger and also the color of these.
No, that's music play.
Now you can see our logo at the Hamburger is visible London.
OK, what else is remaining is they have to make this certain, I find the bar and display this button
and this menu, the playlist.
So let's make those things.
So we already have this sort of standard.
Bill is with West Ham.
All we have to add time and also this place is.
But it's at a time, audiences.
So everything is done, but things are private and the music name and the picture.
So let's add a profile, Victoria.
So let's create a section song name.
Okay.
Or song pages, second song Bridges, oh, sorry.
Listen to that, it's playing this song.
OK, so we have done with our music interface, so let's make that Blaze list, no.
Like this one?
So we are done with our head.
So one thing is to many that.
To create a world front page, the first page that is going to be our logo.
So this is my point.
So this looks like this, so I know you wouldn't you would ask me then will look different.
And in the next video, the last thing is remaining is that to act prototype so that the world is ready
and I will do it in the next one.