Welcome back in this, we're going to do overtime for our music player.
So let's start prototyping.
As you can see, I have four frames on my screen.
Let's start from the first frame.
So select the frame, learn to prototype panel.
So I'm going to join the first frame to set everything.
And let's add a smart animation audio.
And never get to never get to iPhone 13, Pro Max one.
And the animation is an instant, so let's choose smart animation.
OK, now to second frame, this is an ostrich in the song.
So if you click on this button for Britain, then the song is going to change.
And the film is going to be disturbing.
So let's choose on one.
And contoured film user can go on the second line like this.
And all the settings will be sitting on this.
And from here, the playlist is going to open.
Let's choose Martin Mission over here.
I think we are done with protecting so.
So let's prevent it.
So it was this that or the smart generation you can see, you can see the logos on the top now.
And I won't pretend the song, so I'm going to click on this fall button.
This is the second song.
And from here, I can go back to my first song.
From this playlist bottom, I can access playlist like this.
You can see this cool animation, but I can't go back because I said the protection for this playlist,
so let's do that first.
So from this, it has to go onto the second thing.
Elizabeth smart animation now this played again.
OK, if I click on this button, you can see the list is going Donald.
And just open it again.
Close, you can also see the animation effect audio you.
This looks really cool.
So this is the time for our music player app, so the secretaries and others who are in the next room
or in next project.